foreign
this is why God says
right after denying this believing God's
revelation says nothing is conceived
from God
because he knows what their hearts are
doing what they are really believing or
not
and based on that
they are isolated from Quran they cannot
see it
the other the other parts were covered
very nicely by Latifah
verses are things that we may not be
able to understand
or fully comprehend yet
there were Generations wouldn't
understand what what God meant by by the
Earth being egg shaped
that didn't make sense to them
and had they wasted their time
trying to interpret that
we'll just do that Western time and they
may end up confused
there are things in Quran now that we
cannot comprehend
so that reserves this future Generations
because every generation has to see
something new in the Quran
but for our purposes
we have a certain understanding of them
and we have to be content and satisfied
with those
as long as we're not digging and causing
a lot of confusion
I mean it's perfectly right to study the
Quran and try to understand everything
without
we're confusing ourselves
the past generations for example they
didn't understand opened up at 19 men
they had no way of knowing what the
number 19 there
so God gave them a temporary
understanding that there are possibly
the gods of Health
19.
but after the number 19 God gives the
general statement that the gods of head
are engines it was just a general
statement
and that statement served to get them
satisfactory interpretation of the time
will understand it
because
God knows that it is not important
whether the people know the parent is
guarded by 19 or 19 million or what
it's not a Christian thanks to the
doctrine or the worship of God Alone
at the end of verse 7 here says indeed
only those who possess intelligence will
take you
the Quran
people who do not believe in God
the people who do not worship God the
Lord we have to be stupid
they are not intelligent
when God was walking the seventh
University in his hand
and they leave him and they seek the
wisdom of a human being who lived on
earth
a hundred years
who was very tiny
helpless
you know that has to be stupid
the Sun and the Moon
he knows what the sun and the moon are
doing
but they go see the wisdom of a man who
didn't know that what the sun is coming
from
the sun rises every every day from the
East we used to think it's a new Sun
and you don't blame them
that was the extent of the knowledge but
to go to them for the wisdom
that's not intelligent so only those who
are intelligent will worship God Alone
wonderful prayers that you can use
anytime
12 say to talk to those who disbelieve
you will be defeated
then end up in hand on the miserable
above
and the Book of the Quran Hadith that
you'll see at the end
uh an advertisement
for the for the book itself it was just
put in the back
and it asks the question doesn't make
any sense that 3 million Israelis defeat
consistently defeat 150 million hours
consistent
I mean even on the physical level it
doesn't make sense
is this what God says well
because those people have given the
Quran
when you are given the Quran your
responsibility is immediately bubble
now people in this country who come to
Islam and they come to Quran and then
they end up for them Hadith and soon
these people are in bad shape
they are much better off as Christians
worshiping Jesus
because when they their hand with the
Quran who are practically every page
says worship God Alone
don't go to anything else
get the responsibilities is Multiplied
many poles
the Quran is a fantastic blessing
what a fantastic disaster
depending on if you upload it or not
so the Arabs
were given the Quran
and they chose to abandon
that's disastrous they don't need it
so number 12 applied to them
say to those who disbelieve
you will be defeated
then end up in hell and the miserable
Above This God's promise and it doesn't
matter what the physical statistics say
you may be 200 million
but you disbelieved God when you said
the Quran is complete and perfect
you will be defeated
doesn't matter how many you are how rich
you are how many weapons you have how
much weapons you have
200 million Arabs
and God gave them so much well
just to make all the physical statistics
on their side
yep they keep losing
it's just completely people
and it's because they abandoned the
Quran
the Quran is in their tongue in Arabic
if they don't
need
demonstrated that to them last night
that which words do you take you take
the words of God for the words of
someone who said that the prophet said
you might go a step further I say do you
take the words of God or there wasn't
the prophet if the prophet walks through
this door and shows you his passport
proving that he is muhammadullah and he
tells you something that's different
from the Quran you're going to take the
words of God or the words of Muhammad
I will put the question backwards but of
course
the Hadith Muhammad as you would see in
the last person that both of us is
coming
I said Muhammad Muhammad
they are the hadiths of people whose
grandparents even the grandparents or
their grandparents never saw the crop
this is
do you follow what God said they follow
things that were sent by people who said
that the prophet said
amongst those 200 million ads I'm sure
if somebody shows in the tree I'm sure
so many of them
to the student
so he would not survive
someone that was not I know what he's
saying is yeah
I can't say by the way
but there must be somewhere
else
oh
it's not the Hadith from Jesus either
Mark Luke Matthews and John
that's what the gospels are these are
the canonized books
they're canonized because they uh in the
conferences of Nicene they collected all
the
scriptures
of Jesus the true and the fourth
I'm very
they colonize this for and burned
everything else and they established the
doctrine of the father of the son of the
Holy Spirit
if you don't believe it you go to any
encyclopedia or even some dictionaries
under my scene
time of businesses
[Music]
in Egyptians
love messenger
for sure
well even even nowadays we have these
six
red Crystal's promise Muslims
I mean they are very respected Scholars
who wrote the book the midst of God
incarnate and their censored and costs
and everything by the rest of the
Christian world
at verse 12 explains the people of the
Arabs
you want to competitors
take the next stage
she's a tough act to follow but
yeah
you can do it
and exactly has been said
the class one was fighting in the power
of God
they saw each other twice
throwing in the eyes of the people